From the silk sheets... to the mean streets...
Trouble is a animation, adventure, family film directed by Kevin Johnson.
A pampered dog named Trouble must learn to live in the real world while trying to escape from his
former owner's greedy children and must learn how to survive on the big-city streets.
Trouble (voice), played by Big Sean.
Rousey (voice), played by Pamela Adlon.
Zoe Bell (voice), played by Lucy Hale.
Claire (voice), played by Marissa Jaret Winokur.
Norbert (voice), played by Joel McHale.
Thurman (voice), played by Wilmer Valderrama.
Trouble, also known as Dog Gone Trouble, is a 2019 animated comedy film, directed by Kevin
Johnson, and starring Sean "Big Sean" Anderson, Pamela Adlon, and Lucy Hale.
It was the final film role of Betty White before her death in 2021 (not counting her appearance in
the 2022 documentary Betty White: A Celebration, which was released posthumously).
It was also dedicated in memory of executive producer,
Conrad Vernon's dog, Linus who died in 2017.
The film was released on May 28, 2021, by Netflix.
The film explores themes of squirrel, singer, dog.
The tone is lighthearted.